<level name="Stretchable Electronics Virtual Experiment" startin="WORLD_OFFICE">	
    <objective descrition="Weigh out and cure the PDMS">
        <dialog type="intro">
			<line cutscene="professor" cue="talk">
				Lets start by making a stretchable electronic circuit. 
			</line>
			<line>
				Creating a circuit that can be stretched or flexed would allow us to put electronic systems into the fabric of clothes or even inside the human body. 
			</line>
			<line>
				The secret is start with a versatile stretchy substance you can build your circuit on. A chemical called PDMS is ideal.
			</line>
			<line>
				Find the weighing scales and weigh out XXg of PDMS
			</line>
		</dialog>

		<goal target="stretch_scales" reward="curing_pdms" />

		<dialog type="outro">
			<line cutscene="professor" cue="talk">
				Well done!
			</line>
			<line cutscene="stretch_weighstation" cue="one">
				PDMS stands for Polydimethylsiloxane. It’s a clear, non-reactive, non-toxic, silicon-based substance. Liquid PDMS is used in shampoos to make your hair look shiny. Solid PDMS is used to make contact lenses. 
			</line>
			<line cutscene="stretch_weighstation" cue="two">
				You control its consistency by adding XX??, a curing agent/cross linker?? Let’s add XXml.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="stretch_weighstation" cue="three">
				The PDMS is now beginning to transform from a liquid into a rubbery substance. 
			</line>
			<line cutscene="professor" cue="talk">
				Before it solidifies we need to remove any air bubbles and shape it into a thin layer. Better hurry up!
			</line>
			<line>
		        Find the vacuum chamber
		    </line>
		</dialog>		
	</objective>
		
	<objective description="Vacuum the PDMS">
		
		<goal target="stretch_vacuum" reward="air_free_pdms"/>

		<dialog type="outro">
			<line cutscene="cutscene_vacuum" cue="one">
				That’s it. The vacuum removes the air bubbles.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="professor" cue="talk">
				Now we need to spin the PDMS into a thin layer. The spin coater is the tool for that.
			</line>
		</dialog>
	</objective>
	
	<objective>
		<goal target="stretch_spincoater" reard="pdms_membrane" />
		<dialog type="outro">
			<line cutscene="cutscene_spincoater" cue="one">
				Great. If we pour the PDMS onto a smooth silicon disc and spin the disc at XXrpm our fluid will spread into a nice even layer.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_spincoater" cue="two">
				0.2 millimetres thick! That’s perfect.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="professor" cue="talk">
				Now we need to add our conducting circuit. For that we need to make a mask. Find the lab’s mask cutter.
			</line>
		</dialog>
	</objective>
	
	<objective>
		<goal target="stretch_printer" reward="pdms_with_electrodes" />
		
		<dialog type="outro">
			<line cutscene="cutscene_maskcutter" cue="one">
				To make the mask the precision cutting machine (what’s this machine called?) cuts holes out of a thin sheet of plastic. The pattern of holes is the shape of our circuit. 
			</line>
			<line cutscene="professor" cue="talk">
				Now we can use the mask to add a conducting metal to the PDMS with the evaporator machine. 
			</line>
		</dialog>
	</objective>
	
	<objective>
		<goal target="stretch_evaporater" reward="gold_pdms" />
		
		<dialog type="outro">
			<line cutscene="cutscene_evaporator" cue="one">
				The PDMS layer and the mask go into the top of the evaporator and a gold pellet is placed at the bottom. Then we pump out the air to create a vacuum inside. 
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_evaporator" cue="two">
				The machine heats the gold until it evaporates. With no air molecules to get in the way, the gold particles/atoms? rise up and collect on the areas of the PDMS not covered by the mask. Like water droplets condensing under the lid of a pot of boiling water.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_evaporator" cue="three">
				Now you have a perfect circuit of gold electrodes on a rubbery base layer.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="professor" cue="talk">
				But just as normal electric wires need to be covered by a layer of insulation, before we can use our stretchable circuit we need to cover the exposed electrodes with a protective layer of PDMS.
			</line>
			<line>
				Head back to the weighing station to mix more PDMS.
			</line>
		</dialog>
	</objective>
	
	<objective>
		<goal target="stretch_scales" reward="coated electrodes" />
		
		<dialog type="outro">
			<line cutscene="professor" cue="talk">
				In this batch of PDMS we need a special ingredient that will trigger the curing process when exposed to UV light. 
			</line>
			<line>
				As before, the spin coater spreads the new layer into a thin film. 
			</line>
			<line>
				Now comes the tricky part – the photolithography machine.
			</line>
		</dialog>
	</objective>
	
	<objective>
		<goal target="stretch_photolithography" reward="stretchy_circuit" />
		
		<dialog type="outro">
			<line>
				The photolithography machine will blast our new layer of PDMS with UV light. The circuit slides into the bottom and above it we need to position a ‘shadow mask’ – a glass slide that is mostly clear apart from a few tiny dark areas.
			</line>
			<line>
				Control the aligner machine to position the dark areas of the mask over the ends of the gold circuit.
			</line>
			<line>
				Good! 
			</line>
			<line>
				Now when we turn on the UV light, the top layer of liquid PDMS is exposed and begins to cure into to a rubbery texture. 
			</line>
			<line>
				The areas covered by the dark areas of the mask are shielded from the UV light and the PDMS remains in its liquid state. We can wash these bits away to leave a few tiny sections of the gold circuit accessible to connect wires to. 
			</line>
			<line>
				Our stretchable circuit is ready to use!  
			</line>
		</dialog>
	</objective>

</level>