<level name="Cancer Treatment Virtual Experiment" startin="WORLD_WETLAB" music="musicCancer">
    <objective>
        <dialog type="intro">
            <line>
                Now let's make a new medical treatment for cancer.
			</line>
			<line>
                Nanoscale particles can be engineered to carry drugs to the area of the body they’re needed most.
			</line>
            <line>
                We’re going to make tiny packages that destroy cancer cells using nanoparticles of gold, an anti-cancer drug and an antibody protein that recognizes cancer cells.
            </line>
            <line>
                The first step is to mix two chemical solutions to create tiny gold particles.
            </line>
            <line>
                Find the weighing scales.
            </line>
        </dialog>
        
        <goal target="cancer_scales" />
        
        <dialog type="outro">
			<line>
				Great.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_weighstation" cue="one">
                Now weigh out 0.1g of chloroauric acid powder (gold salt) and mix it with distilled water to form a solution. And then do the same with 0.1g of sodium citrate. 
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_weighstation" cue="two">
                And then do the same with 0.5g of sodium citrate.
			</line>
			<line>
                Now take the two solutions to the Hotplate Stirrer for mixing.
			</line>
		</dialog>
    </objective>
    
    <objective>
        <goal target="cancer_stirbar" />
        
        <dialog type="outro">
            <line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_stirbar" cue="one">
                Heat the chloroauric acid solution, add a magnetic stir bar and then pour in the sodium citrate solution.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_stirbar" cue="two">
                The sodium citrate reduces gold ions into gold atoms.
			</line>
            <line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_stirbar" cue="three">
                The mixture turns red as the gold atoms cluster into nanoparticles. 
            </line>
            <line>
                The next step is to measure your gold particles with the Dynamic Light Scattering machine.
            </line>
        </dialog>
    </objective>
    
    <objective>
        <goal target="cancer_dynamiclight" />
        
        <dialog type="outro">
            <line>
                That’s it. Put a sample of the solution into the machine.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_dynamiclight" cue="one">
                A laser blasts light into the sample and the machine records the light scattered by particles in the solution and calculates their size. 
			</line>
            <line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_dynamiclight" cue="two">
                Your particles are 50nm in diameter. That’s perfect. Particles this size will be able to enter a cancer cell.
            </line>
            <line>
                Now head back to the hotplate stirrer to prepare an anti-cancer nanomedicine.
            </line>
        </dialog>
    </objective>
    
    <objective>
        <goal target="cancer_stirbar" />
        
        <dialog type="outro">
            <line>
                First we need to add an anti-cancer drug.
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_stirbar_2" cue="one">
                The drug is called doxorubicin.
			</line>
            <line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_stirbar_2" cue="two">
                Then add chitosan - a liquid containing long polymer molecules, and give the solution a good stir.
            </line>
            <line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_stirbar_2" cue="three">
                The polymer molecules have linked together, wrapping up gold nanoparticles and the anti-cancer drug into small packages.
            </line>
            <line>
                Now you need to purify the solution. Find the dialysis cassette.
            </line>
        </dialog>
    </objective>
    
    <objective>
        <goal target="cancer_dialysis" />
        
        <dialog type="outro">
            <line>
                Inject the solution into the membrane bag inside the cassette and then place it in some distilled water.  
			</line>
			<line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_dialysisbar" cue="one">
                The excess drug is small enough to pass through the membrane leaving just the larger gold-drug-polymer particles inside. This purifies the solution!
			</line>
            <line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_dialysisbar" cue="two">
                Now we just need to add a final outer layer to the nanoparticles – an antibody, a protein that recognizes cancer cell.
            </line>
            <line cutscene="cutscene_cancer_dialysisbar" cue="three">
                These linker molecules bind to the outside of the nanoparticle and enable us to add the final ingredient – an antibody. 
            </line>
            <line>
                Now you do it!
            </line>
            <line cutscene="minigameCancer" type="game">
                To make a dose of our cancer fighting nanomedicine, we need to mix the solutions in the correct order. Click to mix the different solutions. 
            </line>
            <line>
                Once injected into the body the nanomedicine is small enough to go undetected by the body’s defence mechanisms. The antibody you added binds with receptors on a cancer cell and the nanomedicine is smuggled inside.
            </line>
            <line>
                Enzymes in the cancer cell degrade the polymer capsule and release the drug and gold nanoparticles. The drug then damages the DNA of the cancer cell. 
            </line>
            <line>
                When the patient is exposed to near-infrared light, the gold nanoparticles absorb the energy and convert it into heat, which also helps kill the cancer cell.
            </line>
            <line>
                Nanoparticle treatments like this are currently being tested and offer huge potential in the fight against cancer.
            </line>
        </dialog>
    </objective>
</level>